League of Women Voters, Schenectady County Records apap210
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
League of Women Voters, Schenectady County
1925-2004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap210
10.4 cubic ft.
This collection contains records of the League of Women Voters, Schenectady County.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2005 and 2006.
Historical Note
On April 30, 1925, Mrs. Charles Richmond, wife of the president of Union College, invited approximately fifty women to her home for a talk by Mrs. F.W. Slade, chairman of the New York State League of Women Voters. After Slade's talk, the women at the meeting decided to elect officers and adopt by-laws thereby forming the Schenectady County League of Women Voters (later renamed League of Women Voters, Schenectady County).
The League of Women Voters of the United States is a, "nonpartisan political organization that encourages informed and active participation in government, works to increase understanding of major public policy, issues, and influences public policy through education and advocacy." Originally, the organization began at the National American Women Suffrage Association's 50th convention in St. Louis, Missouri, when President Carrie Chapman Catt proposed the creation of a "league of women voters to finish the fight and aid in the reconstruction of the nation." One year later, on February 14, 1920 – the League was officially created in Chicago, Illinois. At a national level, the League has helped further Social Security, the Food and Drug Acts, as well as the involvement and legal status of women in the United States. The League was also one of the first organizations in the United States to be recognized by the United Nations has a non-governmental organization.
The League contains New York state section, which is divided into counties. The state's leagues get funds from the League of Women Voters of New York Education Fund, which is a nonprofit educational organization. The Schenectady County chapter adopted their bylaws on May 23,1979 and have continued to revise them until 2013. Their bylaws indicate that any person who subscribes to the purpose and policy of the League can become a member. The Schenectady County branch focuses on issues that happen within the Schenectady and Albany areas. Today the Schenectady County chapter supports the Women's Equality Act and works with high school students in the Albany area to promote government participation. The chapter also holds monthly meetings on the benefits of healthcare, local government, and children at risk in the Schenectady County.
Scope and Contents
The League of Women Voters of Schenectady County Records includes eighty years' worth of information about all aspects of the local organization. The 10.4 cubic ft. collection is divided into six series according to the organizational structure and activities of the Schenectady County records, flowing from administrative files to publications that the League created. The collection contains meeting minutes, bulletins, and information on studies done by the organization. These collections will give researchers insight into the rights that the League fought for, the local issues they discussed, the goals they set, and how all of these evolved throughout the years. The League of Women Voters of Schenectady County is arranged alphabetically by format and then chronologically within each format, except for the scrapbooks which are arranged chronologically.
The collection contains information on the city of Schenectady. The League's Schenectady County branch focused on issues in the Schenectady County including their criminal justice system and healthcare facilities like Glenridge Hospital. The League also looked at the committees the County ran, including the committees on the county charter and the county manager search. The League's involvement in the Schenectady County ranged from the years of 1935-2005.
The collection also contains scrapbooks ranging from the years of 1933-1990. The scrapbooks hold newspaper articles that the local League was featured in, as well as photographs of members and local events that the League participated in.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is processed into 6 series.Series 1-5 are arranged alphabetically and Series 6 is arranged chrnologically.
Women; Social Activists and Public Advocates; Schenectady, New York; Public Servants; Education; Social Activists
- Administrative Files, 1925-2004; 1.5 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  The Administrative Files series contains annual reports and meeting minutes of the League of Women Voters of Schenectady County. The collection also contains budget, public relations, social events, and state board announcements.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Annual Meeting, 1936-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting, 1977-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Awards, Community, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Awards, Susan B. Anthony, 1980-1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Budget, 1956-1957; 1969-1980 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Budget, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Budget, 1990-2001 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1936; 1938 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Guidelines, Politcal and Policy, 1980-2005 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Membership Lists: Executive Board and General Membership, 1925; 1940 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Membership Lists: Executive Board and General Membership, 1941; 1959 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Membership Lists: Executive Board and General Membership, 1960-2000 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1925-1936 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - New York Leauge of Women Voters Handbook for Leaders (Historical) with Board Mintues and Committee Noters, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Public Relations and Media Information, 1979; 1982; 1984; 1988-1989; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Public Relations: Radio Spot Announcement and Radio Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Publicity, Newspaper Clippings, 1931-1933 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Publicity, Newspaper Clippings, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Publicity, Newspaper Clippings, 1967-1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, Newspaper Clippings, 1983-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Reports, Financing Education, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Reports and Minutes, 1933-1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Reports, Nominating Committee, 1977-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Reports, Program Planning, Survey 2000, 1954-2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Social Events, 75th Anniversary, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Social Events, Legislative Receptions, 1979-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Social Events, Legislative Reception, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Social Events, Legislative Reception, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Social Events, Organizational Poem 30th Anniversary, ca. 1955 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Reports, LWV State Board - Budget and Membership Crisis, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Reports, LWV State Board - Budgeting and Finance, 1975-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Reports, LWV State Board - Consensus, Membership, Programs, 1976-1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Reports, LWV State Board - Land Use; Social Policy, 1973-1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Reports, LWV State Board, Public Relations, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Reports, LWV State Board, Women and the Law, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Reports, LWV State Board, Women and the Law, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Reports, LWV State Board, Women and the Law, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Reports, LWV State Board, Women and the Law, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Reports, LWV State Board, Women and the Law, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Reports, LWV State Board, Women and the Law, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Reports, LWV State Board, Women and the Law, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Subject Files, 1930-2005; 2.5 cubic ft.
  The Subject Files series contains information on children at risk, domestic violence, and human right campaigns. The collection also features scrips of plays put on by the League of Women Voters as well as information on how to use natural resources and advice on urban planning and voting.
  - Centennial Play: "One Hundred Years A-Growing," Script and Radio Transcript, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Children at Risk: Alliance for Children and Families of Schenectady County, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Children at Risk: The Campaign for Healthy Children, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Children at Risk: Capital District Childcare Coaliton (1 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Children at Risk: Capital district Childcare Coaliton (2 of 2), 1987-1989; 2001; 2003; 2005 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Children at Risk: "Chaos in Sentencing Youth Offenders" and "Crime Doesn't Pay- But You Do!", 1943 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Children at Risk: Child Abuse and Neglect, 1987-1998 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Children at Risk: Childcare; Childcare that Works Campaign, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Children at Risk: Children's Court, 1930-1954 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Children at Risk: Children's Court (County of Schenectady), Department of Corrections Report, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Children at Risk: Children's Health, Child Health Center; "Bright Schenectady Futures - Dr. Kevin Karpowicz, M.D., 2000 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Children at Risk: Citizen's Advisory Committee (County of Schenectady) Correspondence and Probation Department/Case Work Advocacy (County of Schenectady), 1942-1957 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Children at Risk: Citizen's Advisory Committee Minutes (County of Schenectady), 1947-1950 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Children at Risk: Citizen's Advisory Committee Minutes (County of Schenectady), 1952-1956 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Children at Risk: Committee Notes, 1993-2000 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Children at Risk: Daycare, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Children at Risk: Daycare, Newspaper Clippings, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Children at Risk: Juvenile Detention, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Children at Risk: Mental Health, Child Guidance Clinics Information, Mental Health Hygiene Information, 1930-1941 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Children at Risk: Prevention Survey - Development and Draft, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Children at Risk: Schenectady County Prevention Programming, 1991-2001 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Children at Risk: Schenectady County Prevention Programming, Newspaper Clippings, 1996-2001 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Children at Risk: Schenectady County Services/Daycare, 1995-2002 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Children at Risk: Social Security, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Children at Risk: Social Welfare, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Children at Risk: House Action Reports, Conference Summary, "Welfare Reform Agreement," No. 104-105, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Children at Risk: Welfare Reform, 1995-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Children at Risk: Welfare Reform, Newspaper Clippings, 1995-2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Children at Risk: "Youth Correction Authority Act," Offical Draft, and "Youth Correction Authority Law", 1940; 1942 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Children at Risk: The "Youth Problem" in the Community, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - City of New York Charter, Chapter 5-10: The New York City Charter Map, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - CRIME: Conference on Crime, The Criminal and Society, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Displaced Homemakers; Conference, "Changing Labour Force, Changing Family", 1974; 1982; 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Displaced Homemakers; Conference: "Women Returning to the Workplace", 1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Displaced Homemakers; Literature, 1983-1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Displaced Homemakers; Minutes, Agenda, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Displaced Homemakers; Minutes, Agenda, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Displaced Homemakers; Minutes, Agenda, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Displaced Homemakers; Phone Survey Drafts and Development, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Displaced Homemakers: Report of the Taskforce, "Displaced Homemakers in Schenectady County" Draft and Final, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Domestic Violence: HERF (The Hospital Educational and Research Fund), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Domestic Violence: Human Right Commission, Violence Against Women Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Domestic Violence: Human Right Commission, Violence Against Women Task Force, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Domestic Violence: Human Right Commission, Violence Against Women Task Force, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Domestic Violence: Human Right Commission, Violence Against Women Task Force, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Domestic Violence: Human Right Commission, Violence Against Women Task Force, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Domestic Violence: Human Right Commission, Violence Against Women Task Force, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Domestic Violence: Human Right Commission, Violence Against Women Task Force, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Domestice Violence: LWV Minneapollis Publication, "Breaking the Cycle of Violence", 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Domestice Violence, Newspaper Clippings, 1976-2000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Domestic Violence: Office For the Prevention of Domestice Violence, NYS, 1990-1997 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Domestic Violence: Schenectady County Alternatives to Violence Task Force Y.W.C.A., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Domestic Violence: Schenectady County Alternatives to Violence Task Force Y.W.C.A., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Domestic Violence: Schenectady County Alternatives to Violence Task Force Y.W.C.A., 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Domestic Violence: Schenectady County Alternatives to Violence Task Force Y.W.C.A., 2000-2005 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Housing: Housing Assistance in Schenectady, 1964; 1989; 2000 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Housing: LWV vs HUD (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Housing: LWV vs HUD (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Housing: Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Housing: Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Housing: Newspaper Clippings, 1978; 1988-1989; 1991; 1996; 1999 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Housing: Newspaper Clippings, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Human Needs: Community Forum Project, Final Report, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Human Needs: LWV Human Needs Study, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Human Needs: LWV Position Paper, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Human Needs: Meeting Basic Human Needs, Demographic Data, 1980; 1987 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Human Needs: Meeting Basic Human Needs: A Leader's Guide for Phase 1, Undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Human Needs: New Hampshire Times, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Human Needs: Welfare Reform, 1987; 1989-1991; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Human Rights: U.S. Power/UN, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Human Services: Newspaper Clippings, 1980; 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Human Services: Packwood Letter, 1983-04-27 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Human Services: Social Agencies, Schenectady, 1983; 1992 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Inter-League Organization of LWV Capital District (I.L.O.), 1979; 1985 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Legal Aid: Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Legal Aid: Consensus Meeting, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Legal Aid: Final Report "Assigned Counsel or Public Defender for Schenectady County", 1983 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Legal Aid: Newspaper Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Legal Aid: Position Paper: Schenectady Champer of Commerce Support for Public Defender Over Assigned Counsel, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Legal Aid: Position Paper, "Statement on Schenectady's System of Defense for the Indigent," LWV, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Natural Resources: Aquifer, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Natural Resources: Aquifer- Acquifer Committee, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Natural Resources: Aquifer Final Report on Mini- Grant USOE- G007903434, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Natural Resources: Aquifer and Mini Grant, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Natural Resources: Aquifer - Newspaper Clippings, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Natural Resources: Aquifer - Newspaper Clippings, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Natural Resources: Aquifer - Newspaper Clippings, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Natural Resources: Aquifer - Options for the Future: Our Land, Our Water (Conference Program), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Natural Resources: Aquifer- Publications, 1974; 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Natual Resources: ECOS (Environmental Clearinghouse of Schenectady), 1980; 1982; 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Natural Resources: Energy, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Natural Resources: Enviornmental Planning, 1971; 1977; 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Natural Resources; Environmental Protection, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Natural Resources: Environmental Protection, Newspaper Clippings, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Natural Resources: Environmental Protection, Newspaper Clippings, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Natural Resources: Environmental Protection, Newspaper Clippings, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Natural Resources: Hazardous Waste, 1980-2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Natural Resources: Land Use, Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1976; 1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Natural Resources: Land Use Study, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Natural Resources: Land Use, Urban Sprawl, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Natural Resources: Land Use, LWV Publications, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Natural Resources: Waste Management- An Integral Waste Management Program, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Natural Resources: Waste Management- Five League (ILO) Study on Waste Mangement - Inter-League Organization, 1986-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Natural Resources: Waste Management- ILO (Interleague Organization) Board Minutes, Notes, Membership, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Natural Resources: Waste Management- Municipal Solid Waste Composting Study, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Natural Resources: Waste Management, Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Natural Resources: Waste Management - New York State Waste Management Plan; Plus Meeting Notes, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Natural Resources: Waste Management - Positon Proposal, LWV of Albany for the Capital District, 1988; 2001 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Quiz Whiz: What's the U.S. to You? & Quiz, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Scripts: "Wide-Eyed Bride" ERA Play, Correspondence, 1977-1984 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Scripts: "Wide-Eyed Bride" ERA Play, Post Show Questionaire/Panel, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Scripts: "Wide-Eyed Bride" ERA Play Promotion, Performance, Sales, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Scripts: "Wide-Eyed Bride" ERA Play, Skit Development, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Scripts: "Wide-Eyed bride" ERA Play, Variant Scripts, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Urban Planning: Capital District Regional Planning Commission, 1975; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Urban Planning: Newspaper Clippings, 1999-2001; 2005 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Urban Planning: Schenectady, New York, 1976-1993 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Urban Planning: Smart Growth; Urban Sprawl, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Urban Planning: Sustainable Development Conference, Union College, 2005 February 25 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Urban Planning: Urban Sprawl, Smart Growth, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Urban Planning: Urban Sprawl, Smart Growth, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Urban Planning: Urban Sprawl, Smart Growth, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Urban Planning: Urban Sprawl, Smart Growth, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Urban Planning: Urban Sprawl, Smart Growth, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Voter Services: Congressional Interview Report, Crowther, Hon. Mr. Frank, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Voter Services: LWV Election Guide, Newspaper Section, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Voter Services: LWV Election Guide, Newspaper Section, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Voter Services: LWV Election Guide, Newspaper Section, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Voter Services: LWV Election Guide, Newspaper Section, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Voter Services: LWV Election Guide, Newspaper Section, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Voter Services: Party Platform Debate, Gillespie (Democrat) vs Rivers (Republican), 1984 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Voter Services: "Plan C," Schenectady City Government, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, Prepublication Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, Prepublication Materials, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, Prepublication Materials, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Voter Services: Who's Who, Prepublication Materials, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 68)